sticksports.com 2017-12-14

# Privacy Policy - Stick Sports

This Privacy Notice details information regarding the use and disclosure of User Information collected through the Stick Sports Services which includes all games and websites as accessed by mobile, tablet or computing device or via any browser. Stick Sports provides this Privacy Notice to help you make an informed decision about whether to use or continue using the Stick Sports Services 

This Privacy Notice is incorporated into and is subject to the Stick Sports terms of service and end user licence agreement. By using the Stick Sports Services or by submitting any personal information you agree to this policy. 

**INFORMATION**

User Provided Information: You provide certain personally identifiable information (such as your name and email address) to Stick Sports when choosing to participate in various activities on the Stick Sports Services such as registering, posting messages in our forums, entering contests or sweepstakes, taking advantage of promotions, responding to surveys, or subscribing to newsletters or other mailing lists. 

Cookies Information: When you visit the Stick Sports Sites, we may send one or more cookies - a small text file containing a string of alphanumeric characters - to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser. Stick Sports uses both session cookies and persistent cookies, for the purpose of remembering game states, your login status and generally to provide a better experience. A persistent cookie remains after you close your browser. Persistent cookies may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the site. Persistent cookies can be removed by following your web browser help file directions. A session cookie is temporary and disappears after you close your browser. You can reset your web browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some features of the Stick Sports Sites may not function properly if the ability to accept cookies is disabled. 

Flurry analytics tool: We use Flurry in order to develop and analyse use of certain services that we provide. If you wish to opt-out from Flurry analytics, please follow this link: <http://www.flurry.com/resources/privacy.html>

Location Data: Stick Sports may collect and process your location data to provide location related Services and advertisements. We may use various technologies to determine location, such as GPS, Wi-Fi or other network-based data such as IP address. Your GPS geo-location is not accessed without your consent. Stick Sports will not share your GPS geo-location with third parties without your consent. Please note that we may share your anonymous location data with partners in order to improve services. 

Log File Information: When you use the Stick Sports Sites, our servers automatically record certain information that your web browser sends whenever you visit any website. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser type, browser language, referring / exit pages and URLs, platform type, number of clicks, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed and the order of those pages, the amount of time spent on particular pages, the date and time of your request, and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser. 

GIFs Information: When you use the Stick Sports Sites, we may employ "clear GIFs" which are used to track the online usage patterns of our Users anonymously. In addition, we may also use clear GIFs in HTML-based emails sent to our users to track which emails are opened by recipients. 

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, clickwww.networkadvertising.org 

**INFORMATION US** E 

If you submit personally identifiable information to us through the Stick Sports Sites, then we use your personal information to operate, maintain, and provide to you the features and functionality of the Stick Sports Sites. 

Any personal information that you voluntarily disclose online (on discussion boards, in messages and chat areas, within your public profile page, etc.) becomes publicly available and can be collected and used by others. Your account name (not your email address) is displayed to other Users when you send messages through the Stick Sports Sites and other Users can contact you through messages and comments. 

We do not use your email address or other personally identifiable information to send commercial or marketing messages without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out. We may, however, use your email address without further consent for non-marketing or administrative purposes (such as notifying you of major Stick Sports Site changes or for customer service purposes). 

We use both your personally identifiable information and certain non-personally-identifiable information (such as anonymous User usage data, cookies, IP addresses, browser type, location, clickstream data, etc.) to improve the quality and design of the Stick Sports Sites and to create new features, promotions, functionality, and services by storing, tracking, and analysing User preferences and trends. 

We use cookies, gifs, and log file information to: (a) remember information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your visit or the next time you visit the Stick Sports Sites; (b) provide custom, personalized content and information; (c) monitor the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns; (d) monitor aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors, pages viewed, etc.; and (e) track your entries, submissions, and status in promotions, sweepstakes, and contests. 

**INFORMATION DISCLOSURES**

We provide personally identifiable information and non-personally-identifiable information to our subsidiaries, affiliated companies, or other businesses or persons for the purpose of processing such information on our behalf. We require that these parties agree to process such information in compliance with our privacy policy, and we use reasonable efforts to limit their use of such information and to use other appropriate confidentiality and security measures. 

We do not share your personally identifiable information (such as name or email address) with other, third-party companies for their commercial or marketing use without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out. 

We do share non-personally-identifiable information (such as anonymous User usage data, referring / exit pages and URLs, platform types, number of clicks, etc.) with interested third-parties to assist them in understanding the usage patterns for certain content, services, advertisements, promotions, and/or functionality on the Stick Sports Sites. 

We may release personally identifiable information and/or non-personally-identifiable information if required to do so by law, or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a court order, or search warrant. 

Stick Sports also reserves the right to disclose personally identifiable information and/or non-personally-identifiable information that Stick Sports believes, in good faith, is appropriate or necessary to enforce our Terms and Conditions of use, take precautions against liability, to investigate and defend itself against any third-party claims or allegations, to assist government enforcement agencies, to protect the security or integrity of our web site, and to protect the rights, property, or personal safety of Stick Sports, our Users or others. 

**SPECIAL PROVISIONS FOR CHILDRENS PRIVACY**

Stick Sports does not knowingly collect or maintain personally identifiable information or non-personally-identifiable information on the Stick Sports Sites from persons under 13 years of age, and no part of our website is directed to persons under 13. If you are under 13 years of age, then please do not use or access the Stick Sports Sites at any time or in any manner. If Stick Sports learns that personally identifiable information of persons under 13 years of age has been collected on the Stick Sports Sites without verified parental consent, then Stick Sports will take the appropriate steps to delete this information. 

**PRIVACY CHOICE**

You may, of course, decline to submit personally identifiable information through the Stick Sports Sites, in which case Stick Sports may not be able to provide certain services to you. You may update or correct your personal profile information and email preferences at any time by visiting your account profile page. 

To protect your privacy and security, we take reasonable steps (such as requesting a unique password) to verify your identity before granting you profile access or making corrections. You are responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your unique password and account information at all times. 

To manage your settings and to opt-out from targeted advertising please click: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>
